Now, when I had first said that that first time was a hoax, y'all was up in arms, Amanda
Sia was always running her damn mouth, blah, blah, blah.
Remember that?
Do y'all remember that?
Do y'all remember?
The ear?
Remember when I said, now, come on now, y'all.
This is not real.
Folks said, oh my God, Amanda Sia is the worst.
She is terrible.
Remember that?
Consuela remembers.
They was coming.
They was mad.
I ain't been wrong yet.
Okay.
I just, I can't wait for the real Helma to come down by Kamala.
That's when I, that's when I really want it.
So, okay, Mr. Masekela.
Remember, I was walking down the stairs at the house and I said, nah, nah, that wasn't real.
I said, I said, nah, nah, nah, that, that wasn't real.
And folks was upset at your girl.
And I ain't, tell me what time I was wrong last year.
Someone says you only wrong one time a year.
What time I was wrong last year?
You know what time I was wrong last year?
I'm going to tell you.
I said Trump wasn't going to make it the year.
I was wrong.
You right.
He's still here.
Okay.
I was wrong.
She, man.
So, you know, I just, you know, some little jackass on here said, Amanda, what do you do?
I do whatever the fuck I want to.
That's what I do.
I've been, I've been paying taxes since I was eight fucking years old.
So I do what the fuck I want to now.
That's what I do.
Now, the question is, why are you worrying about what the fuck I be doing instead of worrying about what you be doing?
Okay.
Because, baby, I am at retirement age.
I was working when you was learning how to count.
And we were the same age.
Okay.
I mean, someone said, I like you and your take on politics.
Usually when one is deemed problematic in multiple circles, the common denominator is you.
Yes, I am the common denominator.
I am problematic in Hollywood.
I am problematic in politics.
I am problematic everywhere.
Ignorance exists.
And since it exists everywhere, yes, I'm problematic.
Because my whole existence is about elevating our vibration.
Get it?
Yes, I am problematic.
And if you've been following me for a while, and you don't know what I do, then you ain't been following close enough.
So maybe you need to try to follow better.
Mm-hmm.
Nigga gonna ask me, what do you do?
As if I'm not a fucking icon.
Listen, I'm feeling myself only because, man, I'm hoping that the level of absolute obviousness of this nonsense wakes folks up a little bit more.
So, I'm just hoping.
Because the planets, the planets is saying that we got, we got, we got, we got it.
The planets is really behind us saying we got it.
Okay?
So, I'm trying to, I'm trying to really help us get in there.
Really trying to help us get in there.
God damn.
Shit.
So, yes, Jungle XX Cat.
Normalize being a fucking problem to these people.
You ain't never lie.
I am problematic.
Everyone who has ever called me problematic has been somebody I do not respect.
Okay?
Has been somebody I do not respect.
And I do not go back and forth with people that have fake names and no pictures.
You do not exist.
So, you have been blocked.
Bye.
Mm-mm-mm.
Them people said, we want a ballroom.
You know what we should do?
Do you understand how nutty that is?
There was a team's call about this, y'all.
They sat, they sat somewhere and said, okay, what, what can we, and somebody said, I got it.
Somebody said, I got it.
Here's what we're going to do.
All these people went along with it.
Come on, man.
Come on.
Someone in the comments said, they said they were at work and they said, man, ain't no black man going to run shirtless through secret service.
That don't make no damn sense.
And they said their MAGA co-worker was livid.
Oh, my God.
But I want to tell y'all something.
Whatever is coming that hasn't got you already, the only way to prepare for it is to understand that this world that we're in is completely fabricated and false.
And to divorce yourself from it.
That's it.
If seeing children being ripped from their families while they're put on buses to be sent to detention camps, if that didn't wake you up to see that all of this shit is fake, those people were, in many cases, legal that morning.
They just deported an American citizen to a country that he's not even, he was never from.
So when I see folks concerned and worried and, you know, I see folks talking about we not ready for a revolution because we can't fish and weird shit like that.
I just want y'all to understand that the revolution that is needed is not one of apocalypse.
It is one of the exact opposite.
We are living in apocalypse.
We are living in destruction.
We are living in denigration.
We are living in pollution.
The revolution is the exact opposite.
It's one of growth.
It's one of love.
It's one of expansion.
It's one of care.
Yes, Audeli.
So whatever, whatever you see with all these Democrats and Republicans, all that shit, all that shit, all that shit is fake and it's not going to last.
I just need y'all to understand that we are on the brink of it all falling to the ground and people talking about, well, yeah, but if we don't hold it, nothing we can do is going to hold it up.
I had to realize that myself like, oh, even all this effort to hold up the establishment, it's not going to matter because the wave is coming.
No matter how you build the boat, no matter how you reinforce the boat, the wave is coming.
And those of us who know, we know, we know.
I stood in 2023 and looked upon the ocean and I looked and I saw a storm coming and I said, I said, this is in August of 2023.
And I said, that storm is what's coming to the United States.
That storm right there is what's coming.
Folks don't even know.
Don't worry your mind.
We're trying to latch on or bolster to try to buy more time.
That's not going to buy you time.
That's not going to save you time.
Your time is.
We in a whole other time.
So the best thing I believe you can do is divorce yourself from everything that has been lying to you.
I'm just, I'm just picturing these motherfuckers on the call and somebody said, I got it.
False flag at the White House Correspondents Dinner.
Let's do it.
This man done fell asleep twice in one press conference in the Oval Office.
He was going to stay up at the White House Correspondents Dinner.
Did they start it at two o'clock?
Did they make it a correspondent lunch?
Kimberland, they in the writer's room pitching.
They like, okay, I got a pitch.
White House Correspondents Dinner.
Bear with me.
You know that man eat dinner at five o'clock.
I'm about to block this motherfucker in here.
For real.
I'm about to block this nigga in here who talking about you were on a TV.
Jet GPT said you were on a children's show because I think you in here to try and piss me off.
So, anywho, I decided I'm going to release a chapter of my unreleased memoir this week.
So, if you haven't signed up for my newsletter, go to AmandaSeals.com and sign up so that you can be up on it.
And, um, I'm going to release it for free.
You can donate as a thank you.
Um, but nonetheless, look out for that.
I know, White House Correspondents Dinner.
Got it.
We're bringing me in.
Makes it look smooth, right?
And then we hear pop, pop, pop.
Not inside the dinner because we don't want it to get too crazy.
But loud enough.
To where it's a threat.
Then we scatter.
We scatter, okay?
Now, we're going to have to give everybody specific blocking.
But we scatter, okay?
And so, when the scatter happens, uh, we get, um, we get, uh, we get, we get, we get, we get the eagle in the car out of there.
Then, we're going to get, uh, RFK.
His wife, too?
Nah, I forget his wife.
We get RFK.
Vance is in the meeting.
What about me?
Hey, can we do me first?
I mean, it's going to look kind of weird if we get you first before the president.
So, come on.
I mean, he's going to die tomorrow.
Anyway, we need to make sure that I'm safe.
That would be more realistic.
You're right.
Okay, okay.
So, we're going to get Jance.
We're going to get Jance Dance.
Because that's what the J.D. stand for.
Jance Dance.
We're going to get Jance Dance first.
Um, and, uh, okay.
So, yeah, Jance Dance, you'll go with us.
And then, uh, what about your wife?
I don't know.
She, uh, we'll see.
Um, I'll have her wear flip-flops.
What we're dealing with here.
Cash was so drunk, that man didn't even move.
He said, heck, Seth, look like one of them old marionette puppets.
How'd it do that?
He was so zooted, his chin was damn near fully dislocated from the rest of his jaw.
What a time.
Apparently, this man, Speed, whatever, is in Grenada right now.
I don't watch none of that.
So, if you see anything funny, I want y'all to tell me.
Okay?
If you see him out there and you see anything that look funny style, I want y'all to tell me.
Because I done heard that he an op.
And anytime I see these, these folks just riding around, going to different places, I'm looking at them sideways like, who, who, what, what, what, why, why you need a whole entourage?
What y'all really doing?
You was just in Trinidad.
Now you're in Grenada?
I don't like it.
And let me tell you, and I just want to say this.
I haven't seen any of the stream.
If any part of that stream.
Hold on, let me rate this for Jordy.
If any part of that stream shows Grenadian people swarming him, I want you to know that is also staged.
Because one thing about Grenadians, we not doing none of that.
We not them type of folk.
Grenadians ain't doing none of that.
Okay?
None, none of it.
Because, baby, when I'm in Grenada.
Let me tell you, when I'm in Grenada, the best I get is someone driving by.
Hey, my dog, keep it up.
Keep it up.
So, I feel like it's a lot of op energy.
I see him in Africa.
I see him in the Caribbean.
I don't like it.
I don't, I don't know if there's a piece of the pie that I'm missing.
Like, is this in the, is this, because I don't know.
Is he meeting with Pan-Africanists?
Because if it ain't that, what is it?
I don't know, because Felakuti's son was like, I don't like it.
He said, I don't like it.
He said, I think that he's going around plotting for, doing research for the, the, the satellites.
That's what, that's what this looks like.
That's what this is.
I just got it.
I don't know how my accent went from Nigerian to French, but he got Shakabars on the tour.
Oh, Lord.
You know, this is why I had to tell y'all.
This is why I had to get away from the whole influencer thing.
Don't, don't, don't, please don't put me in there.
That's, that's, please don't put me in there with them.
Please.
Okay.
Please don't put me in there with them.
That's why y'all getting a whole 17 page, single spaced chapter from my unreleased memoir this week.
Because I need y'all to know I'm not the, I'm, I need, I'm, okay.
No.
Lord.
So if you see any funny shit in Grenada, shout out to my cancers.
If you see any funny shit in Grenada, let me know.
They really did that shit in that ballroom.
Okay.
Pitch.
I'm going to do a pitch.
White House Correspondence Center.
False flag.
We get the ballroom.
Bam.
Put it in motion.
Sigh.